Finding Aid for Jennifer Granholm papers, 1992-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Legal Division
  - General Office Records
    - Federal Correspondence
      - Secretary of the Interior Compact Letters
        - Apache Tribe of Oklahoma 2006
        - Arapaho Tribe of the Wind Reservation 2006
        - Assinoboine and Sioux Tribe 2005-2006
        - Augustine Band Indians 2006
        - Bad River Band Indian Tribe 2006
        - Barona Band Indian Tribe 2006
        - Bay Mills Indian Tribe 2006
        - Bear River Band Indian Tribe 2006
        - Berry Creek Indian Tribe 2006
        - Big Lagoon Rancheria Indian Tribe, 20054
        - Big Sandy Indian Tribe 2006
        - Big Valley Band Indian Tribe 2006
        - Blackfeet Indian Tribe 2006
        - Blue Lake Rancheria Indian Tribe 2006
        - Bois Forte Band Indian Tribe 2006
        - Buena Vista Rancheria Indian Tribe 2006
        - Burns-Paiute Tribe 2006
        - Cabazon Band Of Cahuilla Indian Tribe 2006
        - Cachil DeHe Band of Wintun of Colusa Indian 2006
        - Caddo Nation of Oklahoma Tribe 2006
        - Cahuilla Band Indian Tribe 2006
        - Campo Band of Digueno Indian Tribe 2006
        - Chemehuevi Indian Tribe 2006
        - Cher-Ae Heights Indian Tribe 2006
        - Cherokee Nation of Oklahoma 2006
        - Cheyenne-Araphao of Oklahoma 2006
        - Cheyenne River Sioux Tribe 2007
        - Chickasaw Nation of Oklahoma 2006
        - Chicken Ranch Rancheria Indian Tribe 2006
        - Chippewa Cree Indian Tribe 2006
        - Chitimacha Indian Tribe 2006
        - Choctaw Nation of Oklahoma 2006
        - Citizen Band of Pottawatomie of Oklahoma 2006
        - Cocopah Indian Tribe 2006
        - Couer d’Alene Indian Tribe 2006
        - Colville, Confederated Tribe of 2006
        - Comanche Nation of Oklahoma 2006
        - Compacts by State 2001-2006
        - Confederated Tribes of Chehalis Reservation 2006
        - Confederated Tribes of Coos, Lower Umpqua and Siuslaw Indians 2006
        - Confederated Tribes of Siletz Indians of Oregon 2006
        - Coquille Tribe of Indians and the State of Oregon 2006-2007
        - Coushetta Tribe of Louisiana 2006
        - Cow Creek Band of Umpqua Indians of Oregon 2006
        - Crow Creek Sioux Tribe of the Crow Creek Reservation, South Dakota 2006
        - Delaware Nation of Oklahoma 2006
        - Dry Creek Rancheria Indian Tribe 2006
        - Eastern Band of Cherokee Indian Tribe 2006
        - Eastern Shawnee Tribe of Oklahoma 2006
        - Eastern Shoshone Tribe of the Wind River Reservation 2007
        - Elk Valley Rancheria 2006
        - Elm Indian Colony 2006
        - Ewiiaapaayp Band of Kumeyaay Indians 2006
        - Flandereau Santee Sioux Indian Tribe 2006
        - Fond Du Lac Band Indian Tribe 2006
        - Forrest County Pottawatomie Community 2006-2007
        - Fort McDowell Yavapai Nation 2006
        - Fort Mojave Indian Nation 2006
        - Fort Sill Apache Tribe of Oklahoma 2006-2007
        - Gila River Indian Tribe 2006
        - Grand Portage Band 2006
        - Grand Traverse Band of Ottawa 2006
        - Grande Ronde, Confederated Tribe of 2006
        - Hannahville Indian Community 2006
    - Government Shutdown 2007
    - Intergovernmental Agreements
      - Detroit Area Regional Transit Authority (DARTA) 2003
      - Detroit Wayne County Health Authority 2003-2004
      - Early Childhood Investment Corporation (ECIC) 2005
      - Land Bank Fast Track Authority (LBFTA) 2004-2005
      - Michigan Economic Development Corporation 2003-2006
      - Michigan Home Based Child Care Council (MHB CCC) 2005-2006
      - Operation Jump Start 2006
      - Quality Community Care Council (QCCC) 2004
      - Tribal Water Accord 2004
    - Legislative
      - General 2007
      - 2003-2004
        - Initiatives and Proposals
          - Ad Rules
          - Auditor General
          - Budget and Finance
          - Campaign Finance
          - Child Support
          - Election Law
          - Gas Prices
          - Judiciary
          - Local Government
          - Metro Authority Communications
          - Public Transit
          - Racinos
          - Redevelopment Fast Track Authority (RFTA) Land Banks
          - State Fair Authority
          - Toyota Conveyance
            - General
            - Litigation
        - Messages for Signed Bills
          - FY 2006 Signed Letters for Budget Bills
          - General
        - Special Messages
        - Veto Messages
      - 2005-2006
        - Initiatives and Proposals
          - Baby Bond
          - Base Conversion Authority
          - BIG Bond
            - Background Information and Research
            - Public Act Documents -- Verification
            - General
          - Broadband Authority
          - ChoicePoint
          - Corporate Responsibility
          - Elections
          - Ethics
          - Fire Service
          - Health Care Fair Share
          - Human Trafficking
          - Mackinac Bridge
          - Michigan Economic Growth Authority (MEGA)
          - Merit Award
          - Real Estate Services
          - Single Business Tax (SBT)
          - State Officers Compensation Commission (SOCC)
          - Tax Reversion
        - Messages for Signed Bills
          - 21st Century Jobs
          - 21st Century Schools
          - Clean Michigan II
          - Cobo
          - Constitution and Resolution of Budget Deficits
          - Elections
          - Energy
          - Film Incentives
          - Government Efficiency Commission
          - Health Care
          - IDs
          - Item Pricing
          - Mortgages
          - Michigan State Housing Development Authority (MSHDA)
          - Quality Community Care Council (QCCC)
          - Reform
          - Removal
          - State Officers Compensation Commission (SOCC)
          - Special Session
          - Taxes
          - Tourism Promotion
          - Transit
        - Special Messages
        - Veto Messages
      - 2007-2008
        - Initiatives and Proposals
          - Cobo
          - Elections
          - Films
          - Financial Emergencies
          - Healthcare
          - Lottery
          - Michigan Economic Growth Authority (MEGA)
          - P3s
          - Recovery and Reinvestment Implementation
          - Reform
          - Removal
          - State Officers Compensation Commission (SOCC)
        - Messages for Signed Bills
        - Veto Messages
      - 2009-2010
        - Initiatives and Proposals
        - Messages for Signed Bills
        - Veto Messages
    - Michigan Task Force on Jail and Prison Overcrowding 2004-2005
    - Proclamations 2003-2007
    - Removal from Office (Kwame Kilpatrick)
      - General 2008
      - Mayor of City of Detroit
        - City Council Submission CD Contents 2008
        - Correspondence 2008
          - Letters from Governor to Counsel
          - Letters from Petitioner
          - Letters from Respondent
          - Letter from Prosecutor
        - Joanne Huls 2010
        - Kilpatrick v. Governor, Michigan Court Appeal 2008
        - Kilpatrick v. Governor, Michigan Supreme Court 2008
        - Kilpatrick v. Governor, Wayne Circuit Court 2008
          - Affidavit of Governor
          - Motion to Strike Thomas Affidavit
          - General
        - Linked Documents 2008
        - Pleadings 2008
          - Filed by Petitioner
          - Filed by Respondent
          - Issued by Governor
          - General
        - Wayne County Criminal Proceedings 2008
        - General 2008
    - Reports to Legislature
      - 2003-2009
      - Clemency Reports to Legislature 2003-2010
    - State Administrative Board 2003-2010
- Policy Division
  Regina Bell headed the administration's Policy Division, which advised the governor on a wide range of policy issues. The office also served as a liaison between the governor and cabinet members. Staffers worked in teams assigned to one or more policy areas corresponding to the major divisions of state government. The Policy Division series contains twelve subseries: Director's Files (Regina Bell); Transportation; Foundation Liaison Office; Housing, Urban, and Workforce Development; Public Health; Human Services; State Police, Corrections, and Energy; Agriculture, Natural Resources, and Environmental Quality; Education (Policy Advisors Niya Hardin, Sue Carnell, and Chuck Wilbur); Education (Chuck Wilbur); Benton Harbor; and General Office Records. The files primarily consist of research materials and printed email messages. The files in the General Office Records subseries are arranged both by staff member and by subject. They document the division's work in developing and overseeing Cabinet Action Plans and ensuring departments acted in accordance with the Granholm administration's official policy positions. The General Office Records subseries also documents Granholm's major policy accomplishments.
  - Director’s Files (Regina Bell)
    - Subject Files
      - Ann Arbor Tiger Grant 2009 (Box 124)
      - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act (ARRA) 2009 (Box 124)
      - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act (ARRA) Broadband 2009-2010 (Box 124)
      - Audits 2004-2005, 2009-2010 (Box 124)
      - Budgeting for Outcomes 2004-2005 (Box 124)
      - Bureau of Fire Services 2007 (Box 124)
      - Center for State Innovation 2008-2010, 5 folders (Box 124)
      - Center for Michigan 2007-2010 (Box 124)
      - Commission on Accreditation for Law Enforcement Agencies 2007 (Box 124)
      - Copper Theft 2007-2008 (Box 124)
      - Department of Community Health (DCH)
        - Drug Courts 2006-2008 (Box 124)
        - Medical Education and Research Panel Report2007 (Box 124)
        - Michigan Pandemic Influenza Coordinating Committee Annual Report 2006-2007 (Box 124)
      - Department of Labor and Economic Growth (DELEG)
        - Council for Labor and Economic Growth (CLEG) 2008-2010 (Box 124)
        - Detroit Learning Labs 2010 (Box 124)
        - Detroiters Working for Environmental Justice 2008 (Box 124)
        - ECAR circa 2008 (Box 124)
        - Energy Efficiency 2008-2009 (Box 124)
        - Goodwill 2007-2010 (Box 124)
        - Green Jobs 2008-2009 (Box 124)
        - Federal Communications Commission (FCC) 2008 (Box 124)
        - MCCA New Jobs Training Program 2008 (Box 124)
        - Metro Authority Annual Report 2009 (Box 124)
        - No Worker Left Behind (NWLB) 2007-2010 (Box 124)
        - Subsidized Unemployment 2010 (Box 124)
        - Workforce Investment Act (WIA) State Plan 2010 (Box 124)
      - Delta/NWA Merger 2008 (Box 124)
      - Detroit Riverfront Transportation 2009 (Box 124)
      - Department of Human Services (DHS)
        - Children’s Rights Settlement 2009-2010 (Box 124)
        - Children’s Trust Fund 2007-2010 (Box 124)
        - Commission on Community Action and Economic Opportunity 2008-2010 (Box 124)
        - Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC) (Box 125)
          - General 2000-2009 (Box 125)
          - Pilot Project Final Report and Model Design 2004 (Box 125)
        - Family Resource Centers 2001-2008 (scattered) (Box 125)
        - Individual Development Accounts (IDA’s) 2002, 2004 (Box 125)
        - JET Plus 2009-2010 (Box 125)
        - Low Income Home Energy Assistance Program (LIHEAP) 2008, 2010 (Box 125)
        - Michigan Community Action Agency Association (MCAAA) 2008-2010 (Box 125)
        - Poverty Summit for Action 2007-2010 (Box 125)
        - Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF) Contingency Funds2007-2009 (Box 125)
        - Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF) Work Participation Rate 2009-2010 (Box 125)
      - Department of Natural Resources and Environment
        - Connecting Michigan Trailways 2007-2008 (Box 125)
        - Correspondence 2004, 2008 (Box 125)
        - Department of Environmental Quality (DEQ)
          - Customer Survey 2009 (Box 125)
          - DBE Programs 2009 (Box 125)
        - Detroit Riverfront Conservancy 2007-2008 (Box 125)
        - USDA Rural Development 2008-2009 (Box 125)
      - Department of Corrections
        - 2nd Chance Legislation 2004, 2007-2009, 2 folders (Box 125)
        - Corrections Reform 2008 (Box 125)
        - Correspondence 2007-2008 (Box 125)
        - Council of State Governments (CSG) Justice Center 2007-2009 (Box 125)
        - Indigent Defense 2002, 2010 (Box 125)
        - Michigan Prisoner Re-entry Initiative (MPRI) 2004, 2008-2009 (Box 125)
        - Prison Food 2008 (Box 125)
      - Department of Technology, Management, and Budget
        - Detroit Demolition Project 2003 (Box 125)
        - National Association of State chief Information Officers (NASCIO) 2008, 1 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 125)
        - Monthly Reviews 2008-2009 (Box 125)
        - Strategic Plan 2004-2007 (Box 125)
        - Strategic Plan 2008-2012 (Box 125)
      - Education
        - ACT Policy Report 2004-2005 (Box 125)
        - Adequate Yearly Progress (AYP) 2004 (Box 125)
        - Clean School Buses Plus 2008 (Box 125)
        - Consolidation and District Size 2004-2005 (Box 125)
        - District of 1st Class Schools Analysis 2008 (Box 125)
        - Early Childhood Investment Corporation (ECIC) 2007-2010 (Box 126)
        - Excellent Schools Detroit 2010 (Box 126)
        - Head Start Centers of Excellence 2009-2010 (Box 126)
        - High School Curriculum 2010 (Box 126)
        - Jobs Fund 2010 (Box 126)
        - Kids count In Michigan 2004, 2009-2010 (Box 126)
        - Michigan College Access Network 2010 (Box 126)
        - Promise Neighborhoods 2010 (Box 126)
        - School-Yard Bullying 2001, 2005-2006 (Box 126)
      - Energy Needs
        - Alternative Energy Media Coverage 2007 (Box 126)
        - Clean Energy National conference/Message Events 2010 (Box 126)
        - Eco-Village in Detroit undated (Box 126)
        - Low Income Residents 2006 (Box 126)
        - Milwaukee Energy Efficiency 2008 (Box 126)
        - Renewables Portfolio Standards (RPS) 2008 (Box 126)
      - Food Policy Council 2006-2010 (Box 126)
      - Foundation Liaison Office 2003-2010 (scattered) (Box 126)
      - Government Efficiency
        - Innovations in American Government Award 2010 (Box 126)
        - Cost Cutting Consolidation Concepts 2009 (Box 126)
        - Creating Government That Works Better 1993 (Box 126)
        - Detroit Renaissance 2006-2008 (Box 126)
        - Department of Management and Budget (DMB)/Department of Information Technology (DIT) Merger 2009 (Box 126)
        - Department of Natural Resources (DNR)/Department of Environmental Quality (DEQ) Consolidation 2009 (Box 126)
        - Governing Magazine Measuring Performance 2008 (Box 126)
        - Government Performance Improvement Initiative (GPII) 2008 (Box 126)
        - Government Transparency 2009 (Box 126)
        - Michigan Business One Stop 2010 (Box 126)
        - Michigan Business Services Improvement Initiative (MBSII) 2008 (Box 126)
        - Michigan Measures undated (Box 126)
        - Next Great Companies 2008 (Box 126)
        - Streamlining Michigan State Government 2008 (Box 126)
      - Governor’s Council on Physical Fitness 2008 (Box 126)
      - Grant Award Notices 2009 (Box 126)
      - Health Care
        - General 2007, 2010 (Box 126)
        - Dillon Pooling Plan 2009 (Box 126)
      - Homeland Security
        - Detroit 2007, 2009 (Box 126)
        - Emergency Management Division 2003-2008 (Box 126)
      - Hurricane Katrina 2005 (Box 126)
      - Immigration Law 2010 (Box 126)
      - Interagency Directors Meeting 2007-2009 (Box 126)
      - Internet Innovation Alliance 2008 (Box 126)
      - Jail and Prison Overcrowding 2005 (Box 126)
      - Keeping Michigan Working 2007-2010, 2 folders (Box 126)
      - Land Use Council 2003-2009 (scattered) (Box 126)
      - Lead Abatement 2003 (Box 126)
      - Michigan Commission for the Blind 2008-2009 (Box 127)
      - Michigan Department of Transportation (MDOT)
        - Strategic Plan Updated 2004 (Box 127)
        - 9 Mile Fuel Tanker Incident 2010 (Box 127)
        - Annual Report, Michigan Transportation Fund 2007 (Box 127)
        - Border Crossing 2004-2005 (Box 127)
        - Disadvantaged Business Enterprise (DBE) 2008-2010 (Box 127)
        - Detroit 2009 (Box 127)
        - Detroit River International Crossing (DRIC) 2008-2010 (Box 127)
        - Environmental Assessment Study Results 2004 (Box 127)
        - Federal Motor Carrier Safety Administration, U. S. Department of Transportation (USDOT) 2004 (Box 127)
        - Five Year Road and Bridge Program 2003 (Box 127)
        - Grant Funding Through the Transportation Economic Development Fund Category a Grant Program 2005 (Box 127)
        - Heritage Routes 2003 (Box 127)
        - I-75 Expansion 2004-2005 (Box 127)
        - Jobs Project Bonding Strategy 2005 (Box 127)
        - Jobs Today Initiative Project List and SAFETEA LU Earmarks Project Strategies 2005 (Box 127)
        - M1 Rail 2009 (Box 127)
        - Mackinac Bridge Authority 2004-2005 (Box 127)
        - Michigan House Public Transit Sub-Committee undated (Box 127)
        - Michigan Transportation Economic Development Fund 2004 (Box 127)
        - New Mobility 2008 (Box 127)
        - Passenger Rail Service 2003 (Box 127)
        - Prioritization Process Overview 2004 (Box 127)
        - Sault Ste. Marie Bridge Authority 2010 (Box 127)
        - Southeast Michigan Council of Governments (SEMCOG) Regional Report 2007 (Box 127)
        - St. Clair County Critical Infrastructure Resiliency Assessment 2005 (Box 127)
        - Transportation Equity Act
          - A Legacy for Users (TEA LU) 2004 (Box 127)
          - For the 21st Century (TEA-21) 2003 (Box 127)
        - Task Force 2 (TF2 Transportation Funding) 2008 (Box 127)
        - United States Department of Transportation (USDOT) 2010 (Box 127)
      - Michigan Economic Development Corporation (MEDC)
        - Community Development Block Grant (CDBG) 2009-2010 (Box 127)
        - Center of Energy Excellence 2010 (Box 127)
        - EB-5 Foreign Investment 2009-2010 (Box 127)
        - Entrepreneur 2009-2010 (Box 127)
        - Marquette County Ambassadors 2009 (Box 127)
        - Michigan Economic Development Corporation (MEDC)/Detroit Economic Growth Corporation (DEGC) Partnership 2009 (Box 127)
        - Northwest Michigan Regional 2009 (Box 127)
        - Strategic Plans 2007-2009 (Box 127)
        - Supplier Diversification Fund 2009 (Box 127)
        - Tech Town Fast Trac 2010 (Box 127)
      - Michigan Future 2006, 2008 (Box 127)
      - Michigan League for Human Services 2009 (Box 127)
      - Michigan Reform Agendas 2007-2010 (Box 127)
      - Michigan State Housing Development Authority (MSHDA)
        - QAP 2007 (Box 128)
        - Consolidated Plan 2010 (Box 128)
        - Emerging Cities Summit 2010 (Box 128)
        - Board Meetings 2010, 2 folders (Box 128)
        - Cities of Promise 2006-2010 (Box 128)
        - Cool Cities 2004 (Box 128)
        - Detroit 2008-2010 (Box 128)
        - Detroit Youth Foundation 2006-2007 (Box 128)
        - Hardest Hit Fund 2010 (Box 128)
        - Housing/Foreclosures 2009-2010 (Box 128)
        - Housing Production Report 2009-2010 (Box 128)
        - Idlewild 2010 (Box 128)
        - Michigan Conference on Affordable Housing 2010 (Box 128)
        - Neighborhood Stabilization Program (NSP) 2008-2010 (Box 128)
        - New Market Tax Credits 2007 (Box 128)
        - Sense of Place council 2010 (Box 128)
        - Sustainable Communities Fund 2010 (Box 128)
      - Midwestern Governors Association (MGA) 2007-2010 (Box 128)
      - Military Policy 2005-2008 (Box 128)
      - Military and Veterans Affairs
        - Michigan Youth Challenge Academy 2007 (Box 128)
        - Michigan Veterans Homes Marquette and Grand Rapids 2007 (Box 128)
        - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) 2007 (Box 128)
        - State Homeland Security Grant Program 2005 (Box 128)
        - Reorganization 2005 (Box 128)
      - NAACP 2005, 2010 (Box 128)
      - National Governors Association (NGA) 2005-2009 (Box 128)
      - P3 2007-2008 (Box 128)
      - Payments in Lieu of Taxes 2009-2010 (Box 128)
      - Performance Measures 2007-2008 (Box 128)
      - Predatory Lending and Mortgage Refinance 2008-2009 (Box 128)
      - Real ID 2007-2008 (Box 128)
      - Reinventing Government Brookings Institution 1998 (Box 128)
      - SMART 2008 (Box 128)
      - State of the State 2008-2010, 2 folders (Box 128)
      - Streamlined Sales & Use Tax Compliance 2008-2010 (Box 128)
      - Surgeon General 2004-2008 (Box 128)
      - Treasury Service Tax 2007 (Box 128)
      - Urban Agenda
        - CEO for Cities 2010 (Box 128)
        - Miscellaneous 2004-2009 (Box 128)
        - Signed Documents 2009 (Box 128)
      - US Conference of Mayors 2009 (Box 128)
      - Workplace Flexibility 2008 (Box 128)
    - Department Data Submitted for the Continuation of the Planning Process 2008, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - Detroit Public Schools
      - Agreement Detroit School District & Detroit Federation of Teachers Local 231 2005 (Box 129)
      - Bobb, Robert 2009 (Box 129)
      - Calloway 2006-2008 (Box 129)
      - Deficit Elimination Plan 2005 (Box 129)
      - Diagnostic Financial Assessment 2009-2010 (Box 129)
      - Emergency Financial Management (EFM) 2009 (Box 129)
      - General 2005-2007 (Box 129)
      - Office of Retirement Services 2009-2010 (Box 129)
      - Transition Team 2004-2005 (Box 129)
      - Reports and Analysis 2003-2008 (Box 129)
    - Helping Hand Data 2009-2010 (Box 129)
    - Constituent Correspondence by Subject
      - “Securing Michigan’s Future: The Plan,” 2002 (Box 129)
      - Education and Job Training 2002 (Box 129)
      - Labor and Commerce 2002 (Box 129)
      - Community Safety and Civil Rights
        - General 2002, 2 folders (Box 129)
        - Anishinabeg -- The Original People: Grand Traverse Band of Ottawa & Chippewa Indians, 2000 (Box 129)
          (VHS Cassette)
      - Environment 2002, 2 folders (Box 129)
      - Transportation 2002 (Box 130)
      - Agriculture 2002 (Box 130)
      - Families and Children 2002, 3 folders (Box 130)
      - Health 2002, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - Constituent Correspondence by Correspondent’s Last Name
      - A-M (Box 130)
      - N-Z (Box 131)
  - Foundation Liaison Office (Karen Aldridge-Eason and Maura Dewan)
    - Preparing Students & Workers for Tomorrow 2007 (Box 131)
    - Urban Fresh Food Roundtable 2008 (Box 131)
    - Children’s Cabinet/Funders Meeting 2005 (Box 131)
    - Children’s Cabinet and Foundation Representatives Site Visit -- Harlem, NY 2005 (Box 131)
    - Creating a Health Michigan 2006 (Box 131)
    - Foreclosure Crisis 2008 (Box 131)
    - Foundation Liaison Advisory Committee (FLAC) 2004-2010, 3 folders (Box 131)
  - Transportation (Policy Advisors Jeff Donofrio and Ben Kohrman)
    - 2009 Transportation Program (Box 131)
    - University Region Integrated Transportation Program 2009 (Box 131)
    - Aerotropolis 2006 (Box 131)
    - Airports 2008 (Box 131)
    - Blue Water Bride Authority (Box 132)
      - Plaza Study 2006-2007 (Box 132)
      - CDs and DVDs 2000-2007, 9 optical discs DVDs; 2 folders (Box 132)
      - Draft Environmental Impact Study 2007, 5 folders (Box 132)
    - Detroit Area Regional Transportation Authority (DARTA) 2006-2007 (Box 132)
    - Detroit River International Crossing (DRIC) 2004-2008, 5 folders (Box 132)
    - Grand Region 2009 High Impact Presentation, 2009 (Box 132)
    - I-75 from M-102 to M-59 Oakland County Draft Environmental Impact Statement 2003 (Box 132)
    - Interlocal Agreement Southern Links Trailway 2007 (Box 132)
    - Local Jobs Today 2006-2008 (Box 132)
    - Metro Region 2009 High Impact Presentation, 2009, 1 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 132)
    - Michigan Heritage Routes 2007 (Box 132)